Petit Gargantia
So many details behind the war with
.the Hideauze have been hidden from us.
I don't know what to think anymore.
I shall help you understand.
Earth
A long time ago, the Earth
.started to rapidly cool down,
and humans began looking
.for ways to survive.
So cold...
This doesn't sound very exciting.
One group, the Continental Union, searched for
.habitable planets outside the Solar System.
Continental
Union
Yes.
The other group, the Evolvers, used artificial
.evolution to adapt to non-Earthian conditions.
Evolvers
That's right.
As the ideological conflicts
.between the two parties escalated,
the Continental Union successfully
.engineered the wormhole drive.
Wormhole
Humans thus expanded their territory
.into interstellar space.
Very clear and easy to
understand, Chamber!
So?
What do you mean?
Why did we end up in a war
with the Hideauze?
No idea.
How can you have no idea?!
You remembered all these random
Earthian words and phrases!
As the remaining time
.is dangerously short,
retreat is advised.
Wait! I won't settle for this!
Retreat.
I said, wait!
See you next retreat.
Don't you mean "next week"?!
No idea.
Petit Gargantia!