Petit Gargantia
Hey, how did you like the dried fish?
I've never tasted anything quite like it before.
Not a hit, huh?
Well then, is there anything good from where you're from?
Like, any local specialties?
Yes, plenty.
Protein, vitamins, minerals, and carbohydrates.
Protein
Vitamins
Minerals
Carbohydrates
Eh?
In the Galactic Alliance of Humankind,
one consumes nutrients merely to fuel one's metabolism.
Not a very exciting life.
Do you do anything fun at all?
"Fun"? What do you mean?
You don't enjoy eating, but what about playing?
5 more
hours
Ugh...
Battle simulation.
Sleep?
Defeat the
Hideauze
Okay...
Sleep-development learning.
What?!
None of those things are fun!
How could a guy who's had such a boring life live in our fleet?
I'm kinda worried.
I concur.
Oh, so this is where the short movie's happening?
See you next week.
Petit Gargantia.