Petit Gargantia
That was some serious
running you did, Ridget!
It was nothing.
She ran from the Oceanus,
situated at the front of the fleet,
The Oceanus
to the rear patrol boat where
.the funeral was talking place,
The Oceanus
Rear Patrol Boat
a linear distance of
.about four kilometers.
About
I knew the fleet was large,
but not that large.
There's no way I could
.manage that without a kite.
You hardly notice it
.when you're desperate.
Analyzing Commodore
.Ridget's body data.
Her stamina is among
.the best in the fleet.
Stamina
Among the Best
Really?!
Her chest measurement,
or what Earthians call the "bust,"
Among
the Best
is also among the best.
I guess that's true.
Is it?
Correction.
They are simply the best.
Simply                         the Best
Was that correction necessary?!
As for Amy's measurements,
after Melty, her chest is
among the smalles—
See you next week!
A-Amy?
Petit Gargantia.