Petit Gargantia
You've done it again, Ledo.
We told you time after time
.to leave the whalesquids alone.
The first "Second Lieutenant Ledo's
.Best Fish for the Saba Break" rankings.
The 1st
Second Lt. Ledo's
Best Fish for the Saba Break
Rankings
Where'd that come from?!
The 1st
Second Lt. Ledo's
Best Fish for the Saba Break
Rankings
The 1st
Second Lt. Ledo's
Best Fish for the Saba Break
Rankings
Second Lt. Ledo's
Best Fish for the Saba Break
Rankings
1st Place
In first place...
Rankings
1st Place
Straight to first place?!
The limited running time
.leaves us no choice.
R-Right.
In first place, we have the Saba fish,
1st Place
because the move is
.called the Saba Break.
Because "Saba Break"
Boring!
No twist whatsoever.
Wait, what's a Saba Break?
Because "Saba Break"
A move where you grasp your
opponent's loincloth with both hands
and use your stature and weight to snap your opponent's lower back.
You sure know some
.very strange things.
What's a loincloth?
Loincloth
A type of equipment worn
.around the waist.
Loincloth
I don't even know what's
.going on anymore.
Around here
Those damn Hideauze even carry equipment around their waists?!
Conceptual
Image
Whoa, what a moron!
They're talking to each
.other just fine, though.
Is that Galactic thingymabob full of people like you?
How rude of you
to call me a moron!
The Saba Break.
You grab hold of your opponent's
.equipment and bear down on him.
All right. I understand.
No, you don't!
See you next week.
Petit Gargantia!