Petit Gargantia
Chamber!
Chamber, you've shrunk!
So have you.
What's this?
Your body to head ratio has been reduced by approximately seventy percent,
Body to Head
and your cuteness has increased by over nine hundred percent compared to your regular self.
Cuteness
+
What's... happening to me, Chamber?
Result: only one matching entry.
Result
Matching Entries:
One
Its existence has long been hinted at—a short movie.
Short Movie
Really?
According to the entry,
Ledo
its purpose is to provide more information pertaining to
Age 16
2nd. Lt.
Amy
Age 15
Chamber
Super Cool
the characters that appear in the main series while "having a bit 'o fun."
Age 16
2nd. Lt.
Age 15
Super Cool
I-I see.
So, what's the mission?
Furthermore, the running time is extremely short,
and this movie will be ending imminently.
What? Already?!
Isn't it great that we can talk to each other here?
See you next week.
Petit Gargantia!