Petit Gargantia
Hey, do octopuses really look
that similar to Hideauze?
Anytime
Yeah.
Especially their tentacles.
Oh? I'd like to see that!
Chamber!
Anytime
Hideauze
Like this.
Oh, I see...
They are lifeforms from outer space
that the Galactic Alliance has been
.trying to eradicate for a very long time.
They have organs that emit powerful energy
.beams, as well as a tough exoskeleton.
Energy beam
comes from here
Exoskeleton
Energy beam
comes from here
What's an "exoskeleton"?
Energy beam
comes from here
It is comparable to the clothes
.that Earthians wear.
Anytime
Hideauze
Energy beam
comes from here
Exoskeleton
Anytime
Hideauze
Energy beam
comes from here
Exoskeleton
Anytime
Hideauze
Energy beam
comes from here
Exoskeleton
Anytime
Clothes
Exoskeleton
Huh? Our clothes aren't that stiff!
We couldn't dance in them otherwise.
The Earth really is a peaceful place
.compared to the Alliance.
Such fragile apparel would
.be impossible to fight in.
Not that I mind, Chamber, but why do
you have such detailed pictures of us?
I am an interface system that supports
.and oversees the development of pilots.
I exist solely to set you up for success...
See you next week!
Petit Gargantia.