Petit Gargantia
Ledo.
Thanks for everything
.you've done for us.
Yeah.
I should thank you too.
I guess Chamber's gone.
Yeah.
Negative.
Chamber! You're all right?!
I am going strong,
though only conditionally.
Conditionally?
I am currently in ascension mode.
Ascension Mode
That explains the halo
above your head!
Ascension Mode
It's glowing!
This is the ascension mode.
Ascension Mode
Furthermore, the time left for
this mode is extremely short,
and I will reach the limit imminently...
Chamber!
He did it for this movie.
See
you!
He really pushed himself to the limit.
It's lonely without him.
Yeah.
Rebooting in memory mode.
I am an interface system that supports
.the development of tender moments.
Interface System that Supports
the Development of Tender Moments
I exist solely to verify each and every
.decisive step between you two.
I'm not sure if I like this...
I confirm a rise in the numerical
.value of your relationship.
It is very ripe indeed.
I suppose this is not
.a bad way to end.
Petit Gargantia!