Petit Gargantia
I have several additional
.charges for you, Ledo.
More?!
Hehe :P
Reimbursements for the
.contents of the fallen cargo.
Hehe :P
And repair fees for the damage Chamber accidentally caused to the ship after taking off.
Hum...
And—
There's more?!
Chamber and I are one.
One and the same
So those can be settled with
Chamber's work contrib—
One and the same
Not happening.
No wages are paid
.for stand-in missions.
Well?
Was Ledo able to work properly?
Nope.
Oh my.
Wah
There
there
Wah
There
there
Wah
There
there
Wah
There
there
Wah
There
there
Bevel had to cheer him up afterward.
Wah
There
there
Age
You needed moral support
from a ten-year-old?
Whatever.
I go back carving flute.
Resorting to broken speech during difficult situations
is equivalent to running
.away from the enemy.
Pulse Laser, fire.
See you next week.
Petit Gargantia.