Petit Gargantia
I have detected a sharp decline
.in your vital activity.
I just had a terrible experience.
Requesting an explanation of
what "let's shag" means.
Let's shag~
It does not appear in
.my language database.
I, too, was struck by this
.inexplicable fear and confusion.
There's the cutie!
Heya, Ledo!
Good timing.
What does "shag" mean?
Shag
Huh?
Oh, when you were being
chased by the trannies?
Shag
Pretty sure it means that they
.wanna get closer to you.
We wanna get closer
Right, Saya?
Y-Yeah, I guess.
Since they were chasing after you...
Let's get along
it means they want to get along
really well with you!
Th-That's right!
They wanna have se—
I mean, they wanna
be friends with you!
...I guess?
There is still much to learn
.regarding Earthian culture.
All very complex.
Yup!
See you next week!
Petit...
...Shag'it...
...Gargantia!