Petit Gargantia
You actually managed to drive the great pirate Rackage away!
Very impressive.
Glad you could restore your honor.
Yep.
But man, is that Rackage for real?
Great Pirate
Rackage
Age 19
She's only one year older than me!
Can you believe it?
What does she eat to get that big?
That big
Fish, right?
R-Right.
You're quite the talker now that we can communicate, Ledo.
Learning the Earthian language is easy compared to fighting the Hideauze.
I disagree.
Your language proficiency amounts to less than one percent of the total linguistic possibilities.
Language
proficiency
Below 1%
O-One percent?!
I managed to say "thank you" at the end, didn't I?
Thank
you
Confidently
But that was all.
But that was all
Thank
you
Confidently
But that was all
Thank
you
Confidently
But that was all
Thank
you
Confidently
Thank
you
Confidently
Thank
you
Confidently
But that was all
Super
lame
Chamber
Super lame.
Where'd you learn those words from?
Super
lame
Chamber
Super
lame
Chamber
Super
lame
Chamber
Anyway, isn't this short about to end?
No one new's appearing this time?
I am Ridget, the aide representative of this fleet.
See you next week.
Petit Gargantia!