Petit Gargantia
Man, what a nasty surprise!
What do you mean?
Rackage!
Great
Pirate
Rackage
The great pirate, Rackage!
I could've sworn she was just an extra.
Oh, yeah.
Surrender?
Aahh
I thought she was simply bait
.or some sort of joke villain.
Surrender?
Aahh
I'm at a huge disadvantage
now that she's back!
How come?
Competition is fierce enough in the Girl Bloc as it is,
but now I have no chance at all!
What are Melty and Saya talking about?
X
Cutie Alien Bloc
Girl Bloc
Talking Robot Bloc
As the sole member of the Talking Robot Bloc,
it is beyond my understanding.
However, I predict that Rackage is
going to become a tremendous threat
Sexy Bloc
as a member of the Sexy Bloc.
Your understanding of Earthian culture
.has gotten kind of twisted.
Hey, Ledo, Chamber.
What do you think?
Um, I have no idea.
It is a basic strategy to focus your firepower
on the points that would be most likely
to sway the battle your way.
What do you mean?
I predict that pinpoint attacks on the
demographic that has a fetish for flat chests
Flat
Chest
Fetish
would be most effective in your case.
Flat chests?
Fetish?
This isn't working.
See you next week!
Petit Gargantia!
Fetish!