Petit Gargantia
Requesting confirmation of your
.impressions regarding the Gargantia fleet.
Impressions?
What specifically?
Second Lt. Ledo's
Impressions of
Females
Announcement
Requesting that you announce
.your impressions of the females.
What brought this on?
From these short movies,
I have learned that it is standard
for people of the same gender
to gather and talk about
things that they wouldn't
in front of members
.of the opposite gender.
You sure you weren't being tricked?
The claim is indeed dubious.
Nevertheless, I conjecture there is still value
.in the two of us having such a discussion.
All right.
I don't really get it, but okay!
So, what do you want to know?
I will be confirming your
.impressions of the females.
In other words,
what do you think of them?
What do you think of them?
First, Bellows.
Bellows
She's strong-willed.
Ridget
Ridget.
Serious.
Ridget
Melty.
Melty
Petite.
Saya
Saya.
Mild-mannered.
Saya
Wha—
Chamber, are you even listening?!
It seems that your lack of cognitive ability
.caused a temporary loss of my functions.
Lack of Cognitive Ability
I have the vaguest feeling
.that you're insulting me.
What a clodhead.
Amy, is that you?
I was just telling Chamber my impressions
.of the females aboard the Gargantia fleet.
You're a clodhead in this regard, too.
"Carrothead"? What's that?
Clodhead
It is a word used to respectfully describe people
.who are especially perceptive, like you.
I-I see.
As for you, Amy—
It's okay. No need to tell me.
Really, please spare me.
But I'm a "clodhead," right?
Yeah. That's why I don't need to know.
I'm sure it would only
.make me disappointed.
See you next week.
Petit Gargantia!